Kashane Sakhakorn

ksakhakorn@gmail.com (818) 282-3532

Summary

Extremely versatile worker dedicated to getting the job done correctly. Highly self-motivated with excellent time management skills. Organizes and prioritizes work responsibilities while coordinating well with others. Over a decade of experience in different jobs that have required working under pressure, meeting deadlines, collaborating with others, direct sales, and providing customer service. Appreciates the power of hard work and perseverance thanks to a successful immigrant parent and the other a teacher that survived cancer twice. Avid reader, exerciser, family oriented, and determined to accomplish life's goals.

Skill Highlights

- Problem Solving
- Communication
- Strong Work Ethic

- Multitasking and Prioritizing
- Punctuality and Dependability
- Data Analysis and Organization
- Entrepreneurial Attitude
- Fast Learner and Follows Instructions
- Well-spoken
- Extensive experience with computers (70WPM, well versed in Microsoft office and other computer applications)

Employment History

Apogeeze Inc. Data Analyst/Retail Ticket Broker

04/2019 to Present • Full-time

- Analyze event ticket industry, constantly monitor the fluctuating market finding arbitrage
- Collaborate closely with various teams daily, online meetings throughout the workday
- Manage large amounts of money daily, upwards of 5 and 6 figures in peak seasons
- Happily work overtime on salary to gain experience and balance the workload for everyone

Vector Marketing Sales Representative

01/2019 to 07/2019 • Part-time

• Direct sales for Cutco Cutlery, created and prioritized my schedule, called and met clients, delivered demonstrations to sell product

Stock Investor/Currency Day Trader

11/2016 to Present • Part-time

• Online and self-educated day trader/investor in stocks and other securities markets, options, foreign currencies, cryptocurrencies, charting/technical analysis, fundamental analysis

Smart & Final

Closing Manager

06/2009 to 02/2018 • Full-time

- Began as part-time service clerk while attending school, promoted to cashier within 6 months, fork lift certified, transitioned to receiving inventory and vendors
- Night-Crew Lead for 1.5 years, sole key-carrier supervising other employees overnight
- Closing Manager for over 3 years, supervised work of other employees, counted registers and safe, locked store/set alarm, prepared the store for the next day
- Computer work, emails, inventory check, invoice paperwork, received vendors, ordered inventory deliveries, organized payroll schedule, special certification for hazardous waste

Peak Enrichment

Elementary School Staff After School Program

08/2008 to 06/2009 • Part-time

• Supervised classrooms and organized sports activities, multiple schools in Los Angeles, created invoice for management

Brian McCarthy & Associates

Construction Worker

06/2008 to 08/2008 • Part-time

• Construction worker for homes at different job sites, painter, plasterer, carpenter, laborer, cleaner

Gerhardt Gear

Engineer Associate

06/2006 to 08/2007 • Full-time (2 Summers)

- Operated computers and large machinery for gear making, cleaning, cutting, burring, measuring, labeling
- Organized and packaged parts for shipping and handling department

Education

- 2013 Attended California State University, Northridge for 3 years.
- 2009 Graduated Magna Cum Laude from Bishop Alemany High School.

Received the department award for Mathematics for my graduating class.

(references available upon request)